i just i don't know how people showed like i'm realizing that i'm over here trying to figure out
like how how to feel about so many people watching bad bunny and finding like joy in him literally
being on stage with the zionist supposedly dressing zara and also people are like but
he showed like the real things that are dealing that they're dealing with in puerto rico you know
he showed the the working in the cane fields he showed the unreliability of the electricity and
i'm like yeah but he showed that to people who are proud of that work so like even if you're seeing
it and saying like yeah look at him he's showing what we're going through it's like they they know
what you're going through they put you through it um he's but but the other part of this though is
that like what what the most important part of this is like why is anybody at the super bowl anyway these
people how black am i gonna have to get and i don't think it's possible for this uh establishment
to react to a human problem in a human way it's impossible in terms of self-interest it is it's
obviously that inhuman to me if you look at its history and what it's doing now if that is human
then we're something else so i have to assume that they're non-human
you